Greyce Bastos

Cambridge – UK Phone: +44 77 09684293

E-mail: greyce.amorim@yahoo.com.br

GitUser: **greyceamorim**

Date of Birth: 5th October 1986 Nationality: Brazilian Marital Status: Married

Visa Status: Family member of an EEA (No need for a sponsor)

I am an IT professional with over 6 years of experience in development. My backgrounds are:

- .NET: C#, VB.Net, ASP.NET, ASP MVC (windows form and web form).

- Web developer: ColdFusion, JavaScript, Jquery, HTML, CSS3, Bootstrap and Materialize
- Version control: TortoiseSVN, GitHub
- Database: SQL Server, MySQL and PostgreSQL
- Webservices (Rest/Soap)

Education

MBA in Marketing (Incomplete)

02/2012 - 11/ 2012

Business School São Paulo - Laureate International Universities, São Paulo

Technology Analysis and Systems Development

07/2004 - 07/2007

University of Mogi das Cruzes, São Paulo

Experiences abroad

- Interchange in Ireland 06/2013 05/2014
- Interchange in Ireland 01/2013 02/2013

Work experience

Front End Developer

07/2015 - 11/2015

Stefanini: IT Outsourcing & Software Application Development - São Paulo, Brazil

I have developed the FrontEnd project for an Account Management System for Banks. The technologies I have used there were: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Ajax, Web Services, PostgreSQL, SVN, ReactJS, JavaScript ES6, JSON, REST, BOWER, GULP, Bootstrap and Materialize

Developer (Freelance - temporary)

03/2015 - 05/2015

Azix, São Paulo – Brazil

I was responsible for maintenance web application and web forms written by someone else and fix bugs using C#, ASP MVC, Jquery, JavaScript, SQL Server 2012.

Leader Development Team

07/2014 - 05/2015

Superabiz, São Paulo - Brazil

I was responsible for leading a small development team, deploying and customising the TOTVS Fluig Solution – a new and great platform in Brazil that contains:

ECM (Enterprise Content Management)

- BPM (Business Process Management)
- WCM (Web Content Management)
- Social Media
- Identity/Single Sign- on
- Analytics (Dashboard)

The development and customisation was done using JavaScript, Jquery, Bootstrap, HTML5, CSS3, Web Service, Rest and BPM Notation.

While there I was also responsible for:

- Requirements elicitation / process engineering.
- Development of technical documentation.
- Conducting training for the users.

Projects carried out for those companies (Afeet Group, ADESTE Group, Grafite Fairs and Teresa Perez Tourism)

Au Pair/Nanny (Ireland)

09/2013 - 05/2014

Experience with English language and other culture with the help of a host family.
The experiences with kids and host parents were great for my personal development.

IT Volunter

07/2013 - 08/2013

Edge-Export, Dublin - Ireland

• My task there was fixing bugs in Edge-Export system control using VBA for Excel Advanced.

Software Analyst

03/2013 - 05/2013

Azix Informática, São Paulo - Brazil

• I participated of development of the web application for services registry sanitation, validation and standardization of field, rule checking address and all business rules defined by our clients. The service may include load data into operational bases of ERP, CRM with C#, ASP MVC, ASP.NET, DataLinq, Jquery, SQL SERVER 2008.

Software Analyst

02/2011 -02/2013

<u>Equipaindustria.com.br, São Paulo - Brazil</u>

- I have participated in developing an e-commerce customisable and easy to use platform for our clients so that our clients could have their own e-commerce without having to understand programming. That platform was built using ASP MVC, C#, SQL Server 2008, JavaScript, Jquery, CSS3.
- I have also developed internal systems and intranets with ASP.Net (web forms), C#, Jquery, Fluent NHibernate and SQL SERVER 2008.
- And also I have participated in developing windows forms with printing of tickets for register in Petrol & Gas exposition for ITAESA (Partner Company of the Equipaindustria.com.br) and web forms for register online with barcode generation for this exposition.
- In addition to that I have also performed ETL (extracting data from Excel/txt files, transforming it and loading it into SQL Server databases).

• Furthermore, I participated as an internal quality auditor at the company Taquions (Partner Company of the Equipaindustria.com.br).

Developer 12/2006 – 02/2011

Página Viva CRM, São Paulo - Brazil

- I was responsible for SQL Server 2000/2005 databases maintenance, administration and scripts.
- I also participated in the development and maintenance of CRM systems for Nestlé, Bombril, Procter & Gamble using the technologies ColdFusion, HTML, Jquery, CSS, SQL Server and Webservices Soap.
- In addition, I have also performed systems integration using VB.NET (windows form), ASP.NET (web forms) and SQL Server and data mining for marketing campaigns, generating reports for decision making business via Excel Advanced.
- Technologies used: Cold Fusion, Ajax, JavaScript, JQuery, VB.Net, ASP.Net, SQL Server 2000/2005, Excel VBA.

LinkedIn: https://br.linkedin.com/in/greyce-amorim-33413527

Website: http://greyceamorim.github.io/